치킨 정말 맛있다
Oh, my God.
I love this chicken.
그런 말이 있잖아
Oh, you know
what they say,
인생에서 소중한
것들은 공짜라고
best things in life
are free.
그래, 내가 좀 많이
뺏어먹긴 하네
Okay, you're right.
I eat your food a lot.
이러면 어떨까?
Now, how about this?
우리 집 냉장고를
맘껏 쓰도록 해
You can raid my fridge
anytime you want.
엄청난 배려군
Oh, that's
very kind of you.
D셀 배터리 전해질로
Next time I have a hankering to
wash down a D-cell battery
오래 묵은 피클
주스가 필요할 때
with a jar of
old pickle juice,
한번 들리지 뭐
(clicks tongue)
I'll come a-knockin'.
라지, 답변은 언제
받을 수 있을까
Hey, Raj, you didn't
send your RSVP in.
결혼식에 같이
올 사람 있어?
I'm suppose to ask you if you're
bringing someone to the wedding.
다음에 알려줄게
I'll let you know.
최대한 빨리
알려줄 수 있어?
Well, can you make it soon?
자리 배치 문제로
양쪽에서 싸우고 있어
There's a battle royale going on
over the seating charts.
한쪽 코너는 장모님,
나머지 셋은 엄마가 차지했어
In one corner, Bernadette's mom,
in the other three, mine.
난 결혼 피로연이 싫어
Yeah, I hate
wedding receptions.
신랑 신부가 '빌보'처럼
하면 얼마나 좋을까
Yeah, I wish the bride and groom
would take a cue
from Bilbo Baggins.
반지를 끼고 사라지면
모두 집에 갈 수 있잖아
Slip on the ring, disappear,
and everyone goes home.
가이서 교수님
결혼식은 좋아했잖아
Mm, you liked
Professor Geyser's wedding.
그때는 직접 선데이도
만들 수 있었다고
They had a
make-your-own-sundae bar.
기억에 남는 밤이었지
Oh, that was
a night to remember.
견과류만 잔뜩
담아오기도 했어
Do you know, on one trip,
I just had a bowl of nuts.
암튼 생각해둔 데이트가
있으면 알려줘
Anyway, you got to let me know
if you have a plus one.
안 그러면 엄마가
아는 의사를 초대한대
Because if not, my mom's trying
to sneak in the doctor
목 지방흡입 시술을
해준 분이야
who sucked the fat
out of her neck.
알았어
All right, uh, fine.
데이트랑 같이 갈게
I'm coming and
I'm bringing somebody.
총 2명이야
Uh, Koothrappali plus one.
누구랑 가는데?
Who you bringing?
넌 누구랑 가는데?
Who are you bringing?!
나랑 가기로 했어,
넌 누구랑 가?
He's bringing me;
who are you bringing?
왜 이렇게 오지랖이야
Wow, what a bunch of
Nosey O'Donnells.
누군데 그래
Come on, who is it?
비밀이야
I'm not telling.
난 아시안이라
신비주의로 가겠어
I'm from Asia,
I'm mysterious, deal with it.
하워드, 피로연에
선데이 바도 있어?
Howard aren't having
a make-your-own-sundae bar?
없을거 같아
I don't think so.
있어야 좋아
Well, you should.
결혼의 50%는
이혼으로 끝나는데
50% of marriages end in divorce,
선데이 바는 100%
행복한 결말이지
but 100% of make-your-own-sundae
bars end in happiness.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x20
The Transporter Malfunction
Original Air Date on March 29, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
잘 지내셨어요?
Hello, Mummy, Daddy.
How are you?
그래,
딱히 불평할건 없구나
Pretty good.
Can't complain.
곧 불평 시작할걸
Oh, I'm sure you can.
조금 기다려봐
Just give it a minute.
있잖아요
Listen, uh,
할 말이 있는데
there's something
I want to talk to you about.
전에는 마음의
준비가 안 됐지만
I wasn't ready until now, but...
이젠 때가 된거 같아요
I think it's time.
드디어 올 것이 왔구나
It's finally happening.
커밍아웃 하려고?
You're coming out of
the closet, aren't you?
우리는 널 사랑하고
모두 받아들일 수 있어
We love you, and we accept
your alternate lifestyle.
너무 떠벌리고 다니진 마
Just... keep it to yourself.
전 게이 아니에요
No, I'm not gay.
메트로섹슈얼이라고
할 수는 있겠네요
If anything, I'm metrosexual.
그건 무슨 소리냐
What's that?
이성애자이면서
It means I like women
뷰티 제품에
관심이 많다는 거죠
as well as
their skin-care products.
커밍아웃이 아니라면
Well, if you're
not coming out,
왜 크리켓 준결승
도중에 전화한 거니
why did you call us during
the cricket semifinals?
연애를 하고
싶지만 지쳤어요
I'm tired of trying
to meet someone,
대신 구해줬으면 해서요
and I think I'd like you
to help me find a...
제 부인이요
a wife.
확실히 해두자
And just to clarify...
여자를 말하는 거지?
a female wife?
네
Yes!
아들아,
잘 생각했다
Matchmaking--
very smart move, son.
사랑을 보고
결혼하는 것보단 낫지
Much better than
marrying for love.
우리도 사랑해서
결혼했잖아
We married for love.
이보다 더
좋을 수 없지
And it's been
wonderful!
양자 물리학
덕분에 행복해
Quantum physics
makes me so happy.
잘됐네
Yeah, I'm glad.
우주의 벗은 몸을
보는 것 같아
It's like looking
at the universe naked.
(moaning sigh)
(knocking)
얘들아, 시간 좀 있어?
Hi. Guys got a minute?
무슨 일이야?
Sure. What's up?
며칠 전에 쉘든이
한 농담이 생각나서
Well, I was thinking about
Sheldon's little joke
내가 너네 식량을
다 뺏어먹는다고
the other night about me
eating all your food.
그건 농담이 아니였지만
Oh! That was no joke.
But...
네가 오해할만도 하지
I understand your confusion,
내가 익살꾼
역을 맡고 있으니
as I am our group's
resident cutup.
뭐라는 거야
I'm sorry,
네가 익살꾼이라고?
you are our resident cutup?
응
Yes.
증명해봐
Oh, prove it.
똑똑
Knock-knock.
- 누구세요
- 방해하는 물리학자
- Who's there?
- Interrupting physicist.
- 방해하는 물리학자...
- 뮤온!
Interrupting phys...
Muon! (laughs)
광고 찍고 돈이 남아서
Anyway, I got a little residual
check from my commercial,
너네한테 보답할까 했지
and I thought, hey,
how about I get the guys
고마움의 표시로 말이야
a little thank you
to pay them back?
자, 쉘든
So, Sheldon...
ta-da!
빈티지 민트급
(gasps)
A vintage mint-in-box
1975 미고 스타트렉
트랜스포터잖아
1975 Mego Star Trek
Transporter
트랜스포터 액션도 가능해
with real transporter action.
앗싸
Hot darn!
어디서 구했어?
Where did you get that?
스튜어트네
만화 가게에서
From Stuart,
at the comic book store.
만화 가게에 혼자 갔어?
You went to the
comic book store by yourself?
응, 재밌던데
Yeah. It was fun.
내가 들어가니까 두 명한데
천식 발작이 일어났어
I walked in, and two different
guys got asthma attacks.
기분 좋더라
Felt pretty good.
나도 감사의 뜻을 전해야지
This calls for an
expression of gratitude.
그토록 귀하다는
쉘든 허그를 받는건가?
Ooh, am I about to get
a rare Sheldon Cooper hug?
만약 그런다면
귀하다고 하지 않겠지
No, not this time.
Then they wouldn't be special.
고마워, 페니
(clicks tongue)
Thanks, Penny.
별 거 아닌데 뭘
You're welcome.
네 것도 챙겼어
Don't worry,
I didn't forget about you.
Oh...
레너드, 네 선물은...
Leonard, I got you...
라벨기야!
a label-maker!
Wow...
이것도 좋아
No, it's great.
새 제품이네
- Also mint-in-box.
- Mm.
트랜스포터도 샀어
And I got you
a transporter, too!
최고다
Awesome!
빈티지 스팍 피겨랑 세트야
Look, it was actually
designed for
my vintage Mr. Spock
action figure.
트랜스포터에
스팍을 넣어보자
Oh, that's great! Let's open
them up and put him in there.
- 뜯으라고?
- 그럴 순 없어
- Open it?!
- Oh, good Lord, no!
그냥 장난감이잖아
Why? They're just toys.
- 소장가치가 있어
- 민트급이라고
- They're collectibles.
- They're mint-in-box.
하나만 뜯어서
구경하면 안돼?
Come on. Can't we open
one up and take a look?
안돼
(screams)
No, don't!
한번 뜯으면
가치가 떨어져
Once you open the box,
it loses its value.
엄마도 내 처녀성에
대해 같은 얘기를 해줬어
Yeah, yeah. My mom gave me the
same lecture about my virginity.
꺼내서 갖고 노는게
훨씬 재밌더라
Gotta tell you,
it was a lot more fun
taking it out
and playing with it.
데이트하는데 우리가
끼어도 되는 거야?
Are you sure you want us here
when you meet this woman?
응
Oh, yes.
인도 문화에서는
In my culture, it's expected
첫 데이트에 샤프롱이
있는게 정상이야
to have a chaperone
to oversee a first date.
좋은 인상을
남기고 싶기도 하고
Plus, I want to make a good
impression, and no offense,
너네랑 같이 있으면
키가 190cm 같아
but with you guys here,
I look like I'm six-two.
고등학교 댄스에서
수녀님들이 샤프롱을 했었어
The nuns always chaperoned
the dances at my high school.
성령을 모시기 위해
애들 사이에 자리를 비워뒀어
They used to make us leave room
between us for the Holy Spirit.
힌두교도 비슷해
Uh, Hindus do the same thing.
성령 대신에 소를
모시긴 하지만
Except they leave room
for a cow. (chuckles)
오늘만큼은 인종차별
농담 좀 참아줄래?
Listen, I love your charming
racist humor, but any chance
you could not mock
my religion while she's here?
넌 내가 훈제 연어
먹는다고 놀렸잖아
Yesterday, you made fun of me
for eating lox.
훈제 연어를
숭배하지 않으니까
It's different, your people
don't worship lox.
내 사촌이랑
브런치를 한번 먹어야겠네
Clearly, you've never been
to brunch with my cousins.
부모님이 결정하면
결혼하는 거야?
So, arranged marriages--
the parents just decide
and then you have
to get married?
아냐, 나도 선택권이 있어
No, no, I get a say in it.
누가 올지 모르지만
But I'm sure whoever shows up
will be better company
제미마랑 버터워스와의
스리섬보단 낫겠지
than the threesome
I've been having
with Aunt Jemima
and Mrs. Butterworth.
혹시 라제쉬이신가요?
Excuse me, are you Rajesh?
네
Ah, yes.
락슈미씨 맞죠?
You must be Lakshmi.
만나서 반가워요
Uh, nice to meet you.
네, 반갑습니다
Nice to meet you, too.
(chuckles)
제 친구들이에요
Oh! These are my friends.
이쪽은 베르나데트
- This is Bernadette.
- Hello.
여기는 하워드라고 해요
- And this is Howard.
- Nice to meet you.
편하게 앉으세요
- You, too.
- Please, have a seat.
더블 웨딩이
될 것 같다
(quietly):
I'm thinking double wedding.
쿠퍼 박사
SPOCK:
Dr. Cooper.
쿠퍼 박사
Dr. Cooper?
누구세요?
Is someone there?
책상 위를 보시오
Down here.
On your desk.
스팍?
Spock?
할 말이 있소
I need to speak with you.
흥미롭군
Fascinating.
꿈을 꾸는 중이라고
밖에 설명할 수 없네
The only logical explanation
is that this is a dream.
논리적인 설명은
그뿐만이 아니라네
It is not the only
logical explanation.
코코넛이 머리에 떨어져서
For example,
you could be hallucinating
환각을 보고 있을 수도
after being hit on the head
by, say, a coconut.
코코넛으로 머리를 맞았나?
Was I hit on the head
by a coconut?
답변을 하진 않겠소
I am not going to
dignify that with a response.
중요한 것은
Now to the matter at hand.
트랜스포터 장난감을
갖고 놀아야하오
You need to play
with the transporter toy.
민트급인데?
But it's mint-in-box.
Yes.
상자를 뜯으면
가치가 떨어지겠죠
And to open it
would destroy its value.
하지만 저처럼
But remember, like me,
그쪽도 반은 인간이오
you also have a human half.
나도 답변을 하지 않겠어
Well, I'm not going to
dignify that with a response.
생각해보게
Consider this.
장난감의 목적은 무엇인가
What is the purpose of a toy?
갖고 놀아야 마땅하지
To be played with.
그러니 방치해 두는 것은
Therefore, to not
play with it would be...?
비논리적이군
Illogical.
젠장, 스팍,
네 말이 맞아
Damn it, Spock, you're right.
그렇게 할게
I'll do it.
쉘든, 잠깐
Sheldon, wait.
먼저 깨어나야지
You have to wake up first.
그러네
Oh, of course.
페이저를 바보 모드로
Set phasers to dumb, right?
(chuckles)
좋아
Goodie, goodie, goodie!
이러면 안돼
This is wrong, this is wrong.
신나지만 이러면 안돼
I'm so excited,
but this is wrong.
그래도 할거야
I'm going to do it.
하고 있다
I'm doing it.
해냈다
I did it.
(sniffs)
(sighs)
내가 상상했던
1975년의 향기야
That's what I always thought
1975 smelled like.
빔다운 하자, 스캇
One to beam down,
Mr. Scott.
네, 미스터 스팍
Aye, aye, Mr. Spock.
에너자이즈
Energize.
(plastic clink)
안돼
No. No.
망가진건 아니겠지
Don't be broken.
제발 아니길
Oh, please, don't be broken.
내가 무슨 짓을
하게 만든 거야?
What did you make me do?!
생각을 해보자
Okay, okay, think.
논리적 해답이야
It's only logical.
세상에
My goodness,
정말 맛있었어
that was delicious.
초콜릿 라바 케익을
위해 자리 남겨뒀지?
Well, I hope you saved room
for chocolate lava cake.
멋지다
Impressive.
그런건 어떻게 만들어?
What goes into
making something like that?
초콜릿 수플레로
시작했는데
Well, you start
out by trying to
실패하면 이름을 바꾸고
make chocolate souffle,
and when it falls, you panic,
라바 케익이 되는 거지
quickly change the name,
and voila, lava cake.
I bet our parents are dying toknow how things are going here.
I bet our parents are dying to
know how things are going here.
어디 보자
Well, let's see.
부재 중 전화가
3통이나 왔네
Yep, three missed calls.
전화 4통, 문자 2개
Four missed calls,
two text messages
영상통화 시도까지,
내가 이겼다
and a failed video chat.
I win!
(chuckles)
뭐라고 말해드릴까?
So, what are
we going to tell them?
잘되고 있다고 하려고
I'd like to tell them
things are going well.
나도 그래
Me, too.
너무 기대하실 수 있으니
But before we get
their hopes up,
서로 확인부터 하자
we should probably make sure
we're on the same page.
그래
Okay.
넌 어떤데?
What page are you on?
난 스트레스를
많이 받고 있어
I'm on the one
where I'm under
a lot of pressure
부모님께선 내가
결혼을 하길 원하셔
from my parents to get married
and settle down
and have a family,
게이라는걸 들키지 않게
결혼할 생각이야
and I'm going to do it
so they don't find out I'm gay.
뭐라고?
Say again?
난 게이야
I'm gay.
남자가 남자를...
Like... dude-on-dude,
여자끼리?
but with women?
위장 결혼으로
속이고 싶지 않지만
I know a fake marriage
isn't an honest way to live,
너도 커미아웃이
얼마나 힘든지 알잖아
but you of all people
should know how difficult it is
to come out in our culture.
나도?
Why me of all people?!
뉴델리에서 그런
소문을 들었어
Well, there's a rumor
back in New Delhi that you're--
어떻게 말하지
how shall we say--
사리를 입는게
더 편하다며?
comfortable in a sari.
난 게이가 아냐
I'm not gay!
정말?
초콜릿 케익도 만들고
Really? The chocolate lava cake,
화장실에 귀여운 비누
the little soaps
in the bathroom, and I'm sorry,
나보다 향수도 더
많이 뿌렸으면서
but you're wearing
more perfume than I am.
Khloe and Lamar의
Unbreakable이야
That's Unbreakable
by Khloe and Lamar.
유니섹스 향수라고
And for your information,
it's unisex.
빈칸을 채워봐
Fill in the blank.
I love the nightlife...
I like to boogie.
그럼 그렇지
Got you.
여자랑,
여자랑 추고 싶다고
With women! I like
to boogie with women!
실망이네
That's disappointing.
내가 딱 원하던
게이 남편이였는데
You were exactly the kind
of phony-baloney husband
I was looking for.
고마워
Thank you.
다시 말하지만,
내 거시기는 여자를 좋아해
And once again, my
baloney likes girls.
잠깐
W-W-Wait!
한입 먹기 전에
You don't want to put a
bite of that in your mouth
홈메이드 샹티이
크림을 찍어먹어야지
without trying my
homemade Chantilly cream.
그래, 이번에는
좀 게이스러웠어
Yeah, okay,
that time I heard it.
이런
Oh, dear.
태양이 두 개인데
썬크림을 안 발랐네
Two suns and no sunscreen.
쉘든, 안녕
Hello again, Sheldon.
꼬마 스팍,
이번에는 무슨 일이야?
What is it now, Tiny Spock?
정말 실망이다
I am very disappointed in you.
장난감을 망가뜨리고
바꿔치기 했잖아
You broke your toy
and switched it with Leonard's.
부끄러운 줄 알아
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
갖고 놀라고 한 게 누군데
You're the one who told
me to play with it.
엔터프라이즈호에서
뛰어내리라면
If I told you to jump off
the bridge of the Enterprise,
그렇게 할 거니?
would you do it?
엔터프라이즈에 올라탔다면
Oh, if I got on the bridge
of the Enterprise,
절대 안 떠나지
I would never, ever leave.
좀 지나면 지겨워져
Trust me, it gets old
after a while.
쉘든, 네 잘못을
바로 잡아야 해
You must right
your wrongs, Sheldon.
안 걸렸는데
Why? I got away with it.
레너드도 장난감이 있고
열어볼 일이 없을테니
Leonard has his toy,
and he's never going to open it,
망가진걸 모를 거야
so he won't know it's broken.
내 장난감은
잘 작동하고
And I have a toy
that isn't broken.
모두 행복하지
Everybody's happy.
난 행복하지 않아
Well, I am unhappy.
너네는 감정 못
느끼지 않아?
I thought where you come from
they don't have emotions.
난 대만의
어느 공장에서 왔지
I come from a factory
in Taiwan.
똑바로 행동해
Now, do the right thing.
그거 알아?
You know what you are?
너 때문에 기분
확 잡쳤어
Well, you're
a green-blooded buzz kill.
널 보내야할 시간인거 같아
Perhaps it's time
you beam on out of here.
그래
Fine.
트랜스포터를 사용하지
I will just use
the transporter.
아, 맞다
Oh, right.
네가 망가뜨렸지
You broke it.
알겠어
Very well.
엔터프라이즈호로
빔업 요청
Cooper to Enterprise,
one to beam up.
에너자이즈
Energize.
(roaring)
(screaming)
(grunts softly)
꼬마 스팍, 도와줘
Tiny Spock, help.
점심 먹을까?
Ready for lunch?
잠시만
Yeah, one sec.
엄마한테 들키지
않아서 다행이다
Oh, good.
Ma would've killed me
교정기자 부러졌거든
if she found out
I broke my retainer.
Hey, uh...
저기, 락슈미에 대해서
말할게 있어
can I run something by you?
It's about Lakshmi.
응, 어떻게 돼가?
Yeah, sure.
How are things going?
조금 문제가 있어
We hit a couple
of bumps.
맨해튼 비치에 살아서
She lives
over in Manhattan Beach,
한 시간 걸린대
so it takes, like, an hour
to get there.
그리고 레즈비언이야
And she's a lesbian.
레즈비언이라니?
What do you mean,
"she's a lesbian"?
우리가 바에서
여자를 꼬시다 실패하면
Well, you know how
whenever you and I would try
to hit on women in bars
and they'd blow us off
걔들이 게이일거라고
서로 위안했잖아
and then we'd tell each other
they were probably gay?
그거랑 비슷한데
It's like that.
이번에는 사실이야
Except this time, it's true.
그럼 데이트는
왜 나갔대?
Then why did she even
go out with you?
위장 결혼할
남자를 찾고 있었대
She was looking
for a husband so she can
appear to be straight.
처음에는
미친 짓 같았지만
And, you know,
it sounded crazy
to me at first...
실제로 고려 중이야
but I'm actually
thinking about doing it.
미친 짓 같아 보이는건
Okay, so the reason
that might sound crazy...
정말 미친 짓이라 그래
is 'cause it's crazy!
하워드,
너도 잘 알잖아
Look, Howard,
you're in a relationship.
타협은 어느 정도 필요해
You know you have
to make compromises.
내가 하는 타협이라곤
어떤 침대보를 살지
Yes, but my compromises
are about which bedspread to buy
빨래는 누가 해야할지
or whose turn
it is to do the laundry,
베르나데트 아니면
우리 엄마 차례인지
Bernadette's or my mom's.
좋은 기회야
It's a great deal.
서로 부모님을
안심시키고
We both get our parents
off our backs,
매일 텅 빈 집으로
돌아오지 않아도 돼
I don't have to come home to an
empty apartment every night.
결혼을 하면
다시 탄수화물을 섭취하고
Plus, once I'm married, I
can finally eat carbs again
여유를 갖을 수 있어
and let myself go.
다른 사람을 찾고
싶다고 하면 안돼?
Why don't you
tell your parents
you want to try
to find someone else?
너보다 여자와 경험이
더 많은 사람 말고
Maybe one who hasn't slept with
more woman than you.
이 여자는 나랑
결혼하고 싶어해
Because this one
wants to marry me.
다시는 못 찾을 수 있어
I might never find
another one who does.
섹스도 안 할 사람이랑
결혼할 생각이야?
So you're seriously thinking
about marrying someone
you're never gonna
have sex with?
네가 이러다니
믿을 수 없다
I can't believe your attitude.
동성결혼을
찬성하는 줄 알았어
I thought you were in favor
of gay people getting married.
게이끼리는 괜찮아
Yes, to other gay people!
동성애 혐오자처럼 들려
Do you hear how
homophobic you sound?
(sighs)
망가진 장난감은
갖고 싶지 않아
Oh, I don't want a broken toy.
아무 것도 아냐
Nothing!
뭐?
What?
아무 것도 아니라고
Nothing. I said nothing.
이상하네
That was weird.
그래?
난 이제 적응했어
Really? I don't
even notice anymore.
정말 안 갖고 놀다니
I cannot believe you guys
aren't gonna play with these.
민트급이라고 했잖아
Well, I told you, you don't.
It's mint-in-box.
낭비하는거 같아서
I don't know.
I just think it's a waste.
(squeals)
상자만 보는거 뿐이야
Relax. I'm just
looking at the box.
눈으로 감상해
Perhaps you should
look with your eyes
네브라스카 출신의
남성적인 손으로 만지지 말고
and not your muscular
Nebraska man hands.
대체 왜 그러는 거야?
What is your problem?!
레너드 장난감이 망가질까봐
My problem is that I don't want
you to break Leonard's toy.
방금 흔들어서
망가뜨렸을거 같아
Which you probably
did by shaking it!
봤지?
상자를 흔들었다고
She shook it,
we all saw her.
레너드, 장난감은
갖고 놀라고 사준 거야
Leonard, I bought you this
'cause I wanted you
to have fun with it.
상자에 그냥 두면
무슨 재미야
I don't want it
to sit in this box.
네 말이 맞아
You know,
you're right.
네가 준 선물이잖아
I mean,
it's from you,
절대 팔지 않을 거야
I'm never
gonna sell it.
열어볼게
- I'm opening it.
- Yes!
(nervous yelp)
- 부러졌어
- 뭐라고?
- It's broken.
- What?
이럴 줄 알았어
Oh, nice job, man hands!
내가 그러지 않았어
I didn't break it.
스튜어트가
이런걸 팔았나봐
I guess Stuart
sold it to me like this.
그러네
Yes. Yes, he did.
정말 그럴듯한 설명이다
That is a perfectly satisfying
and plausible explana...
스튜어트 때문이야
Let's all be mad at Stuart!
이거 비싸게 주고 샀어
You know, I paid
a lot for this.
가서 따지자
Let's take it
over there and show him.
그래야지
Absolutely.
잠깐
Wait!
내가 그랬어
It was me.
내가 장난감을 열어보고
I opened your toy...
부러진걸 알았는데
얘기하지 않았어
discovered it was broken
and didn't tell you.
왜 내 장난감을 열어봐?
Why would you
open mine?
거짓말이였어
I didn't. That was a lie.
내 상자를 열어봤는데
I opened my own toy...
부러져 있어서
네 것과 바꿔놨어
and it was already broken,
so I switched them.
스튜어트랑 얘기해봐
You should talk
to Stuart.
그럴 수 없어,
거짓말이거든
I can't, because that was a lie.
지진이 일어났는데...
Yours was broken
in an earthquake--
이것도 거짓말이지
and that's a lie.
진실을 말해봐
What is the truth?
꿈에서 스팍이
나타났는데
My Mr. Spock doll
came to me in a dream
열어보라고 시켰어
and forced me to open it.
장난감이 부러져서
네 것과 바꿨어
And when the toy broke,
I switched it for yours.
스팍이 잘못을
바로잡으라고 했지만
Later, he encouraged me
to do the right thing,
난 말을 듣지 않았어
and I defied him.
그러다가 곤한테
공격당했어
And then I was attacked
by a Gorn.
그건 믿어줄게
Okay, that I believe.
내 행동을 후회하고
있다는걸 알려주고 싶었어
Leonard, Penny, I just,
I want you both to know
that I regret my actions
towards the two of you.
뻥치시네
That's a lie.
저건 내 거야?
So, is that one mine?
응
Yes.
열어보게 이리 줘
Well, hand it over
so I can open it.
그래
Okay.
나한테는 이제
장난감이 없지만
And, Leonard, even though
I don't have one anymore,
너라도 재밌게
놀면 좋겠어
I hope you have fun
playing with it.
- 그것도 거짓말이네
- 너무 뻔하지
And that's a lie, right?
It's a big, fat whopper.
부러지면 좋겠다
I hope it breaks.
생각지 못한 손님이네
This is a treat.
여긴 어쩐 일이야?
What brings
you guys by?
라지, 하위한테
락슈미 얘기를 들었어
Raj, Howie told me what's
going on with you and Lakshmi.
말했어?
You told her?
모두에게 말했어
I told everybody.
너도 언젠가 짝을
구할 수 있을거야
We believe there's
someone out there
who will love
you for you.
그건 논란의 여지가 있지만
Actually, we kind of
agreed to disagree
on that one,
but we both think
아무튼 위장 결혼은
안 하면 좋겠어
you shouldn't
marry this woman.
만날 가능성이 희박한
짝을 기다리는 동안
So, while I'm waiting for
this mysterious perfect match
혼자 외롭게
지내라고?
who may or may not exist,
I'm supposed to just be alone?
네가 껴안을 수 있는
동반자를 준비했어
Not necessarily.
I think
we found someone
for you to cuddle with.
세상에
(gasps)
Oh, my goodness.
너무나 귀여운 요크셔다
Aren't you the cutest
little Yorkie ever!
날 위해 준비했어?
You got him for me?
둘이 잘 어울리거 같더라
Her. We thought you two
would hit it off.
이미 반했어
I think we already have.
너무 고마워
Thank you guys so much.
내 핸드백에
들어가는지 봐야지
Let's go see
if you fit in my man purse.
이래도 이성애자야?
Heterosexual, my ass.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==